Ew!
Ahhh! Ahaaahhhhh!
Ahaaahhhh!
Think of that steel block as Kaido Gamel!
Ahaaaaaahhhh!
Ahaaaah!
Remember your defeat!
Your helplessness!
Hahh...
Ahhh...
Sunder...
Babla!
He's telling that to feel
like it's made of jelly.
No!
Five days remain until the raid.
We will move through Earth's horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
Let's fight for this blue CLS to win.
Take us far away.
Don't give up so I can
come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this rough sensation.
Shut it up, do not be
so afraid to podcast.
You have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times I'll try.
Look and brave it out, it's alright.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to rule the law.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We're a world step ahead.
We will win for sure.
Dreaming on.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the ones that
just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Become the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find things we need for sure.
We will step back.
And we will wait for sure.
So keep moving on.
Oh!
Greetings, my friends.
This is Kinamon.
Pull out your flyers, if you would.
I need you to make an alteration.
Add two lines to the Habu Viper's belly.
Doing so, we'll reveal Lord
Yasui's message to you.
Like this.
Two lines.
Oh, yes, that makes sense.
Yasui's quite clever.
I see.
We got it.
Looking good.
Hey, put your hips into it.
We'll be sailing through rough
waters to reach Onigashima.
We need something sturdy.
You got it, boss!
Mine's on the viper's stomach.
Oh, of course.
I understand, Sakine-mona.
Excellent.
Then all is well.
Hmm?
Sakine-mona here?
I'm getting those ships in tip-top shape.
Super!
Look forward to it.
We got this!
Don't you worry!
Count on us!
I'll go spread the word.
Everyone will know about the change.
You have my thanks.
Pretty impressive.
The people from Wano
can take one look at the
flyer and understand the
message in an instant,
huh?
Hmm.
Let's see if I can figure it out.
You add two lines to Viper.
Viper?
Uh, well, no.
One cannot understand it unless
they know the names of Wano's ports.
Itachi Port.
At any rate, the point is,
each of these ports is associated
with a particular animal.
So with the initial image of the viper,
we implied that Habu port
would be the rendezvous point.
But if you add two lines to a viper,
then they appear as legs, and
with a moment's consideration,
the image of a lizard
will likely come to mind.
Tokage Port is associated with the Lizard.
So, our allies will understand that our
new rendezvous point is the port in Udon.
The flyer is considered a prank,
so there is little chance
that our foes will catch on.
It's truly a marvel.
Lord Yasui deceived the enemy and gave our
thwarted plan a path
forward in one fell swoop.
Our ally to the bitter end.
Alas, it is a debt we can never repay.
If we put his efforts to waste,
it will be our shame as Samurai.
I'm suddenly reminded of his words.
Do you remember what he told us?
We'll become the guardian
deities of Wano itself.
A brilliant man.
Taken too soon.
Of course, a few challenges yet remain,
but we owe much to your efforts.
Furthermore,
our number of allies has increased
and our friends have been reassembled.
Although Dintudo's whereabouts
are still a mystery.
We have seven of the Yakuzaia 9!
All as strong as ever!
This turned around fast.
I think we got a shot.
We need 5,000 troops, right? Correct.
And we're close.
Let's stop patting ourselves on the back.
We're wasting valuable time.
All right.
In that case, let's discuss the plan.
We'll take Kaido's head at any
cost, and Orochi's as well.
We shall do more than avenge Lord Odin.
We'll save this land.
Check it out!
A piece of trivia.
For those determined enough,
there were actually two ways
to enter the land of water.
The first is the dangerous
path that the Straw Hats took,
carried up the waterfalls
by giant koi fish.
The other is to pass through a massive
cave hidden behind one of the waterfalls.
Needless to say,
this will not end well for those
without Kaido and Orochi's permission.
At the end of the cave lies Mogara port.
From there, a gondola will haul up
both crew and cargo to the surface.
After a short trip,
they'll exit the tunnel.
And at last, find themselves in Hakamai.
Ring-a-ding-ding, Kaido, sir.
We're in the house, as one might say.
Ah, just in time.
Didn't think you'd bother coming
back here for the party, Apu.
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
The Golden Festival is here,
and it's gonna be tight!
I never skip out on a party,
or give up on a fight!
It's gonna be wild this year, trust me.
My kind of scene! Yeah!
Now groove with me, boys!
What are those things?
It's the numbers.
The numbers from Wakakashima.
Let's run now.
Or they'll eat us.
Sounds like the numbers have returned.
Those are some messy drunks
if I've ever seen them.
Tell them to go away.
This is just a warm-up.
The real party's right around the corner.
I'll drink to that one more round.
The hell.
They were trying to
kill each other earlier.
Hey, listen up, boys.
Uh, yeah?
We got some important news
about the Beast Pirates.
And the Big Mom Pirates, too.
Let me stand up.
We have decided to form an alliance.
Hooray!
What?
So first things first, we combine
our strength and conquer the world!
Then we can go back to killing each other.
Is this true?
You do not jest! Tell me!
Yes, it's true.
What a blessed day!
Lady Hiyori is alive and
well! That's correct.
I was relieved as well.
My heart aches for Otoko.
She has endured so much pain.
She needs some time to adjust
and will require a guardian.
For now, I shall refrain
from meeting with everyone.
It's for the best.
sentimentality has no place in battle.
Please lend them your strength.
Go to the others.
Find a way to protect the land of Wano.
Princess this is unnecessary.
Please stand up.
You're certain it's her, our
little tomboy's become so elegant.
My she's truly grown up.
Oh Koamatsu, learning of your
imprisonment, we truly fared for the worst.
That's wonderful.
She lives.
I try to do a ha ha ha.
School where is she now?
Is she guarded?
No need to fear.
She is in a safe place at the moment.
This is so delightful to hear.
What a tremendous relief!
She's still alive.
Mama Nisuke!
Hiyori! Drop!
No!
Hiyori...
Zorojuro!
So you were the one who rescued her?
I am grateful.
She hacks a bit rough and tumble,
but she's actually fragile.
That crybaby could be quite the handful.
Easy there.
That crybaby's 18 years
older than you now.
You really gotta get your
mind out of the past, bud.
Whoa!
Ah!
K! Oh no!
So she has a Heinen age advantage now?
I never considered that. Ah!
How long have you known, and
you didn't bother telling me?
That goddess is Momonosuke's sister?
Ah!
What?
Stop staring.
Ah!
Hey, little buddy.
If you need anything, just
come to Uncle Sangoro.
I know exactly what you're doing.
Sir Sangoro, that's enough fooling around.
Kawamatsu, preparations are complete.
It's still not too late.
Are you quite sure?
Yes, we have already come to an agreement.
Sir Hitetsu, this is for you.
It's Kitetsu II.
Second.
It was confiscated from
Luffy Taro and Udon. Here.
Thank you kindly.
He took it from me without permission.
Kitetsu.
I had a feeling it was a famed blade.
Now, my name is Tenguyama Hitetsu.
I am a swordsmith from the land of Wano.
Today's the day.
For two decades,
I have awaited the opportunity to be
in your presence, Lord Momonosuke.
I now bequeath these swords to you.
These were once Lord
Oden's precious weapons.
Ame no Habakiri,
the one who cuts down the highest heavens,
and Enma, the one who slices
through the deepest hells.
Like Shusui, they stand among legends
as two of the 21 excellent Greyblades
What would you like to do
with my masterpieces, my lord?
The choice is yours.
I'm not ready.
But do not mistake this feeling for fear.
I'd merely prefer it if you
kept it for the time being.
As for Enma, it now belongs to you.
However, please heed my warning!
The only man who has ever tamed
that blade was Kozuki Odin himself.
There has never been another.
Try cutting down a tree
to test its fine edge.
Sir Zoro,
I only say this out of the kindness
of my heart, but if I were you,
I would not accept that sword.
He cut off the cliff?
So much of his arm!
Damn it!
Give it back!
It will extract the wielder's Richie all on
its own and always cuts more than needed.
Had you been a normal swordsman,
there would have been but a husk
left behind quite impressive
tell me would you prefer a
different blade nah this one'll
do it i think i could get
used to you and once i do i'll
become a much stronger swordsmen
what an unbelievable fool
keep up the pace you guys we don't
got a lot of time to waste come on
this baby needs to carry
a hundred thousand people
does that seem like a lot you shut up
ain't nothing wrong with airmen for the sky
Let's make a bet!
How many are you thinking?
Madam Orumi, what have you
learned about the enemy?
I was able to gather some helpful intel.
Not to alarm you, but the Beast
Pirates have about 20,000 soldiers,
while Shogun Orochi's army
is about 10,000 strong.
In other words,
we need to be prepared to fight 30,000
enemies once we arrive in Onigashima.
Luckily, we have the mansion blueprints,
but we're still fighting
in our foes' backyard.
though at least it's away
from our homeland we only have
about 4,000 men at best quite
the disadvantage while we are
not plotting an Alto war our
numbers are clearly lacking
nonetheless we must commit to
the plan Terry out the raid,
it's our only opportunity.
Still gotta try!
We're still a mouse man!
He can't run!
That was all wrong too, yes,
you're straining yourself.
I'm gonna need you to
calm your ass down a bit.
Momo, don't you have your
own sword training to do?
I'm focused, so have no fear.
Though, I suppose I do have one
issue that's continued to vex me.
Shoot.
Tsunachi is an exclamation use
to push oneself, yes? Yeah.
Well, Okiku advised me against using it.
It's just a saying some old
guy from my village told me.
Can't really say, I've used it myself.
Whoa!
Hey!
I'm back, master!
Utama!
You had me worried sick!
Hey, Chopper! Luffy!
It's Nami!
Greetings, Kin'emon here.
Sir, Kin'emon.
Koby, Hakuman, Ringo, Udon.
We've gathered 200
additional troops in total.
Incredible!
We now have 4,200 troops!
Although I have yet to hear from Sir Law.
Perhaps we're better off
without his assistance.
Why would you say that?
We need strong people like him!
Nicely done.
You trained so hard that
you're tuckered out now.
Hey, officer!
Hey!
The festival's soon!
Release us!
Not happening! Pipe down! Damn it!
This is our final chance!
Everyone is risking their lives for this!
Unfortunately, there's not much
we can do about the capital.
They have the arrested
parties under a watchful eye.
Even family members protesting
are being locked away.
A true loss, considering that some
of our heartiest samurai are there.
But we must press onward.
Everyone, you have my gratitude.
Use the remaining time for
preparations and travel.
Understood.
We'll meet at the rendezvous
port. Do take care.
I made one for everyone.
We're grateful for your service.
All right, Sir Luffy.
It's time for us to take our leave.
We must get there before
everyone else. Okay.
My group will head out on the sunny.
It's hidden along the coast.
We are as prepared as we'll ever be.
Remember, we're counting on you.
Don't worry.
You can leave it to us.
See you at the port, then.
Countless smokestacks pollute the
skies across the land of Wano.
And beneath them, countless
laborers slave away.
Think it's true?
Do I think what's true?
What Lord Yasui said.
Have you heard that he was covering
for the Akazaya Samurai? What?
He took the fall.
That flyer going around
wasn't his prank after all.
It's the actual signal for the raid.
Bastard.
That's cruel.
Giving us false hope.
The events happened 20 years ago, but
Wano's wounds still haven't healed.
It's hard to believe Kin'emon and the others
are still alive after all these years.
If they are, their
strength has surely faded.
They must have been through so much.
Their spirits would be crushed by now.
There's no hope for a
country this isolated.
We have no outside help.
It would be a complete bloodbath.
We're not strong enough
to face Kaido alone.
Now, seven of the Akazaya nine,
a kunwichi and one young noble press
on with determination in their eyes.
The malnourished land
beneath them trumbles under
their feet like frost
during a bitter winter.
Breaking through the scattered
clouds and rising smog,
the sun shines upon them as the
nine shadows dance like spirits.
Yet these are not vengeful ghosts,
but warriors of flesh and
blood armed with sturdy steel.
It is a tale 20 years in the making.
After we win this battle,
we'll build them proper graves.
I see you've become quite adept.
Huh?
Seems as though Enma
has met a worthy owner.
you already wield kitetsu the third well
that's one of mine too you gotta be kidding
boy have you not questioned
why the famed blade lady Hair
left you feel so comfortable
in your hand it works much
like a cursed blade does the
weak cannot handle them though
there is a much bigger reason
why it feels familiar to you
as you wield it you may find
this shocking but your wado
ichimonji and enma were crafted
by the very same man he was
the legendary blacksmith
shimotsuki kozaburo over 50 years
ago he broke the laws of this
land and left everything behind
lady hyori might have
given you the memento
from her father because
she recognized that sword
enma has yet to be forged into
a black blade its rank will
depend on your actions I'm
gonna have some fun with this
so all is well in Udon must
have been a false alarm yes
no problems to report this
place is under control so please
don't worry about us sir we'll
take care of the prisoners
from here what an untrustworthy
fool he turned out to be
Oh, well.
As long as I have this
intel, this is all I need.
The plans have been changed
from Habu port to Tokage port.
And Kozuki Hiyori still
lives in the north, huh?
Get ready, Kaido!
Gather round.
The sky is clear and the cherry blossoms
flutter about in the flower capital.
The day of the fire festival
has arrived at last.
A historic battle that will affect the
fate of the entire world is about to begin.
Thank you.